Hello everyone!
Hello everyone! I'm Ali Noguchi from Equal Loom!
This is Akihara Saito!
Hi! Hey everyone!
Oh my goodness, I've missed it! It's been so long!
All these guys!
You made me remember!
Do you guys have any ideas?
There is now a boat racing club and a hamburger club.
And one more thing that you may have forgotten is the name of it.
The Ikola Club Game Club!
It's been too long! Remember?
The last time we really did it was on November 26, 2022, on Keara's birthday.
It's been about a year and a half.
You mean it's been a year and a half?
It's been so long!
It's been a long time.
What do you want to do today?
I'd like to invite a guest to play that game today.
That's why I'm inviting you.
Everyone!
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
Please take care of this letter.
No, why? Did you have this prepared?
No, thank you.
Well, Miri's here!
I'm so happy to be here! Wijna was the King of Bomberman twice in Rabbit's Bomberman project.
But she lost the title in the last episode. It was a little bit disappointing, because she practiced a lot.
Yes, I'm practicing. I need practice.
Yes, it's frustrating, but...
I want you to let me train with you in this game, because I want you to be the champion again, so let's train together.
I'd like to explain the rules of this game. There will be three of us and one computer player, for a total of four players.
The first three winners will win the game, and out of respect for Lavitt, the member with the lowest number of wins will be punished by being stripped.
The sum of these three players will win the game, and in respect to Lavitt, the member with the lowest number of wins will be punished with a game of "Ribiri Ribiri.
I was just trying to get him to respect me.
But I was really curious.
Try it.
It hurts like hell.
I don't know, but if the computer wins, we'll all be punished.
Oh, man.
Let's all try to beat the computer.
I'll do my best.
I won't lose.
Let's go play!
Yes, sir.
Okay, so...
What color am I?
Blue.
I'm white.
Pink.
The computer is black.
I can now do it in black.
Here we go.
It's really important that you keep your cool about this.
Stay cool.
Really, really, really calm.
Really.
If you get too greedy, you'll destroy yourself.
I see what you mean.
I don't know if I could've used this.
The one on the right is the glove... the light blue one... and it goes boom.
That's scary.
We did that at Christmas, didn't we?
I haven't done it since then.
I didn't know the rules then.
You're right.
Wow.
2 9 definitely
me
re
Because it's Naccha in kar
rar
ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee ee Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
I can't use my blob.
How are we gonna do that?
What's that?
If you try to kill too many of them.
They'll go cold turkey.
That's a lot of apples.
I'm scared.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
There it comes.
It's not too late.
Next one, next one, next one.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Get after him.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't come any closer.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
It's too strong.
Into the shadows, just in time.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no... oh, no... oh, no... oh, no...
Oh, no... oh, no... oh, no...
Go, go, go, go!
What are you doing?
Oh, that's the worst.
Worst.
Worst...
I'm in a bad place right now
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm quitting.
Boss, hang in there!
Quit, Sir!
Department Manager, hang in there!
I don't want to do this anymore!
There's someone scary!
I'm scared!
Oh, shit!
I'm quitting.
I'll go after him. I'll go after him. I'll go after him.
Oh, shit!
That's cool.
It's cool.
Pull over!
You're gonna have to do it again.
I can't do it again!
That's great, Milia!
Milia is amazing!
That's what I'm talking about!
That's amazing.
LOL!
But I'll only have to do it once.
I just have to make sure I don't let him win three times.
But Hunt won one.
I just have to make sure he doesn't win three.
It's pretty bad, but I'll be fine.
Which one am I? Which one am I? By the way...
What?
It's easy to tell.
Does it end in "weird"?
Does it end in "weird"? I took the liberty.
I was looking right down by mistake.
I was finished.
Wait, this guy...
It's like this, Mukai-kun.
Mukai-kun.
Oh, no!
No... no... no...
No one ever will.
Huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I thought this was going to be a long game.
But now it's over.
I just need one more chance.
Let's do it again.
You're right.
I got it.
Eat it.
It's a deal.
I really don't think I want to do it.
I'd rather not use my right hand.
CURIOSINE: The more you can't use your right hand
The more you can't use it, the more you can't use it
Parking method
I really don't want to do it.
What is this? Blood vessel, blood vessel...
Blood vessel, blood vessel...
What is it?
It's supposed to be used to find things with your eyes.
It's an alarm.
This is 35 out of 100 levels.
Okay, let's go around.
Three, two, one.
Did it light up?
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
He's not in the frame of reference.
Looks like it's in a lot of pain.
Oh, my God! It flew away!
What the...
Joon! Like...
Oh! Oh no!
Does 35 hurt too?
Maybe I was over-enthusiastic.
But I was still kind of surprised.
Like this.
Calmly.
Wow.
Okay, here we go.
What?
I might just do it.
Are you ready?
Three, two, one.
Ahhh...
Is that it? Is it because that's the chair?
Maybe he's just used to it.
Maybe you have a tolerance.
Maybe it's because I made it the tightest.
Maybe I should make it tighter.
Ouch, ouch.
It's so tight.
Loose?
Loosen it.
Why are you making it so tight?
Three, two, one.
Aaaaah!
I want more.
Of course you do.
Is that enough?
One hundred.
Next person to lose gets 100.
I don't want to lose next time.
Let's do the hundred.
The next person who loses will get the 100.
Let's go for the core 100.
We're going to beat the computer.
I know, I made a mistake... and all I did was play Chiara.
We shouldn't do everything together.
Computer.
You're not supposed to move.
Put the bomb on the floor and press the right button.
Don't be mad at me.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey!
It's dead.
I can't do it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
What? What's going on?
What's going on?
It's a tie.
That's great.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, we're fighting the good fight.
Everything's fine.
Oh, I thought you guys were close.
That's good, that's what's left.
It's good, right?
Yeah, it's good. It's even now.
Here, how do you grab this?
Why, why, why, why?
Kya-chan.
What are you talking about?
When did you get this? Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I'm with the computer.
Good luck, mi-chan, mi-chan, mi-chan, mi-chan.
Are you excited?
Are you excited? Okay!
Okay, I'll let this one go.
Run, run, run!
I'm still with you.
Don't worry, we'll win.
I'm so frustrated!
I really don't know what to do!
Wait a minute!
I don't think so.
It could be really
It could be really stupid.
There's nothing but computers again.
Definitely an asshole.
I'm just a fast runner.
Computers heal fast.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Why are you doing this?
Just be quiet.
Hey.
I don't like it.
I really don't like it.
Is it okay?
I'm chillin'.
Chill time.
There's still time.
Oh, my God.
Huh?
Hey, hey.
Yeah!
We did it!
That's great.
I got it.
It's good.
I don't have one of those.
I don't have mine.
I'm left.
Oh, okay, okay.
Hey.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey...
I don't know...
Calm is the most important thing
Calm.
But we won!
I'm so happy. I'm so happy.
It doesn't matter anymore.
All I care about is beating the computer.
You don't mind? For a snack.
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
You're really bad at this.
I'm terrible at this. I'm terrible at this. I'm terrible at this.
No gold walk.
Come on, come on, come on, guys.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
I want to win this thing.
I'm with you.
Safe.
Safe?
I'll never betray Drachma.
Safe.
Not after all.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm glad
So the game club wins!
The planning was done by
Except for the deputy director and the director
The guests win
The guests
Newcomers.
Experience is different
They've had a lot of practice.
I've been watching these two guys for a while now, and their calmness reminds me of my early days, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I want to go back and bloom again, so let's practice together. I don't have a partner, but let's all work together, bon-bon.
I'm going to try my best in the game club
So, do you have any games? No?
You two?
The game club...
Which one do you want to read first?
The two of you from the game section.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't think it's going to have any impact.
Let's try 100.
What?
What? I'll try.
Hold on a second.
Should I do 321? Or...
I don't know.
I don't want to do it.
I'll do the 321.
Is that okay?
Do you mind if I keep the flavor?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay, here we go.
Three.
Three, two, one.
Oh, it hurts!
Does it hurt?
It's stronger than before.
It's 100.
I don't know if I want to do this or not.
Can you do it on 100?
I tried 100.
You can do it?
All the way to Bilbil.
Three, two, one.
That hurts!
Does it hurt that much?
That was amazing.
I've got another life.
It's not gone, it's here.
It was born.
Life is born.
That's amazing.
You want to do it?
I think I'm gonna do it.
Why not?
I was fine earlier.
I was really, really fine earlier.
We won.
Here we go, three, two, one.
Where?
Where is it?
Oh, my God!
Three, two, one.
It hurts, doesn't it?
It hurts.
I know it hurts.
That was fun, chirpy.
That was amazing.
That was awesome.
Bomba Channel
it was a lot of fun!
Thank you all for watching!
Bye bye!